<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../xslt/blog-home.xsl"?> 

<blog>
    <post>
        <number>3</number>
        <title><i>The Tragic in Mark</i> | Review</title>
        <published>February 10, 2020</published>
        <category>Book Reviews</category>
        <link>Jay-TheTragicInMark-2014.html</link>
        <blurb>Jeff Jay explores tragic motifs in ancient literature to argue
            that the Gospel of Mark should be considered a tragic mode of literature. <br></br>
            <i>The Tragic in Mark: A Literary-Historical Interpretation,</i>
            by Jeff Jay. Hermeneutische Untersuchungen zur Theologie 66. 
            Tübingen: Mohr Siebeck, 2014. Pp. xii + 319. Cloth. €124.00. ISBN 9783161532443.
       </blurb>
    </post>
    <post>
        <number>2</number>
        <title><i>Ancient Rhetoric and the Synoptic Problem</i> | Review</title>
        <published>February 2, 2020</published>
        <category>Book Reviews</category>
        <link>Damm-AncientRhetoricReview-2013.html</link>
        <blurb>Alex Damm uses the conventions of ancient rhetoric to evaluate the plausibility of 
            source critical theories regarding the Synoptic Problem. <br></br> 
            <i>Ancient Rhetoric and the Synoptic Problem: Clarifying Markan Priority</i>, 
            by Alex Damm. Bibliotheca Ephemeridum Theologicarum Lovaniensium 252. Leuven: 
            Uitgeverij Peeters, 2013. Pp. xxxviii + 396. Paperback. €85.00. 
            ISBN 9789042926998.</blurb>
    </post>
    <post>
        <number>1</number>
        <title>Localhost for Windows</title>
        <published>January 30, 2019</published>
        <category>Data Publication</category>
        <link>WindowsLocalhost.html</link>
        <blurb>This week we are learning how to setup and run a website from scratch. No safety net, 
            no WordPress, no Divi Builder. Just a text editor.</blurb>
        <heading>Setting Up Your Localhost for Windows</heading>
        <body>
            <p>This week we are learning how to setup and run a website from scratch. 
                No safety net, no WordPress, no Divi Builder. Just a text editor.
                Since I am the only one in the class who seems to use a PC rather than a Mac, 
                I will outline the steps needed to setup a PC to host a local server. Actually, it’s pretty simple to do.</p>
            
            <p><b>Step One</b>: Enable Internet Information Services
                Go to Control Panel -> Programs -> Turn Windows Features on or off
                Ensure that Internet Information Services is selected
                Note: FTP Server does not need to be selected.
                Ensure that Internet Information Services Hostable Web Core is selected.</p>
            
            <p><b>Step Two</b>: Enable WWW Publishing Service
                Go to Computer Management -> Services and Applications
                Select World Wide Web Publishing Services
                Right Click -> Properties -> Startup Type “Automatic”
                Right Click -> Start</p>
            
            <p><b>Step Three</b>: Setup Index in wwwroot folder
                Go to OS(C: drive) -> inetpub -> wwwroot
                Note: There should be two files already there, automatically generated by Microsoft
                Paste or Save HTML files to this root folder</p>
            
            <p><b>Step Four</b>: Open Root Files using Localhost
                Open an internet browser
                In the address bar type “localhost” –> hit enter.
                The browser should display the HTML file labeled “index” (or the first HTML file it comes across)</p>
            
            <p>Congratulations! You are up and running localhost.</p>
        </body>
        <images></images>
    </post>
</blog>
